Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - E
        - Erasure - Drama!, 1989; SR-14167; Erasure (Box 257)
          Catalog # 0-21356; A-side Matrix # 0-21356-A SR1
        - Erasure - Fingers & thumbs (cold summer's day), 1995; SR-14168; Erasure (Box 257)
          Catalog # ED 5817; A-side Matrix # ST ED-66053 A-1
        - Erasure - Oh l'amour, 1986; SR-14169; Erasure (Box 257)
          Catalog # 0-20471; A-side Matrix # 0 20471 A SH1
        - Erasure - Who needs love like that, 1985; SR-14170; Erasure (Box 257)
          Catalog # 0-20404; A-side Matrix # 0-20404AR1SH1
        - Erasure - Sometimes, 1986; SR-14171; Erasure (Box 257)
          Catalog # 12 mute 51; A-side Matrix # MUTE-51-A1
          Mute
        - Erasure - Sometimes, 1987; SR-14172; Erasure (Box 257)
          Catalog # 0-20614; A-side Matrix # 0-20614-A SH-1
        - Erasure - Sometimes, 1987; SR-14173; Erasure (Box 257)
        - Erasure - Chains of love, 1988; SR-14174; Erasure (Box 257)
          Catalog # PRO-A-3186; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-3186-SH-1
        - Eric B. & Rakim - Casualties of war, 1992; SR-14175; Eric B. & Rakim (Box 257)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14176. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # MCA8P 2384; A-side Matrix # MCA-11412 HF-2
        - Eric B. & Rakim - Casualties of war, 1992; SR-14176; Eric B. & Rakim (Box 257)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14175. Multiple copies.
        - Eric B. & Rakim - I ain't no joke, 1993; SR-14177; Eric B. & Rakim (Box 257)
          Catalog # 162-440 448-0; A-side Matrix # 162-440-448-0-A-SP
          4th & Broadway
        - Eric B. & Rakim - Casualties of war, 1992; SR-14178; Eric B. & Rakim (Box 257)
        - Eric B. & Rakim - Juice (know the ledge), 1992; SR-14179; Eric B. & Rakim (Box 257)
          Catalog # MCA12-554381; A-side Matrix # MCA-11150-FDS-1
        - Eric B. & Rakim - In the ghetto, 1990; SR-14180; Eric B. & Rakim (Box 257)
          Catalog # MCA 12-53901; A-side Matrix # MCA 10174 FW2
        - Eric C - I got the flava, 1995; SR-14181; Eric C (Box 257)
          Catalog # 72392 78047-1; A-side Matrix # 72392-78047-1-A
          Street Life Records
        - Eric C - I got the flava, 1995; SR-14182; Eric C (Box 257)
        - Eric C - I got the flava, 1995; SR-14183; Eric C (Box 257)
        - Erickson, Michael - Flashback old school megamix, SR-14184; Erickson, Michael (Box 257)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14185. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # MM-03; A-side Matrix # MM-03 A1
          Megajam Records
        - Erickson, Michael - Flashback old school megamix, SR-14185; Erickson, Michael (Box 257)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14184. Multiple copies.
        - Erotic Drum Band - Love disco style; Jerky rhythm, 1978; SR-14186; Erotic Drum Band (Box 257)
          Catalog # PDS1; A-side Matrix # PDS-1-A
          Prism
        - Erotic Drum Band - Action '78, 1978; SR-14187; Erotic Drum Band (Box 258)
          Catalog # CH-10002; A-side Matrix # CH 10002-AB-2
          Champagne Records
        - Erotic Drum Band - Pop pop shoo wah, 1979; SR-14188; Erotic Drum Band (Box 258)
          Catalog # PDS 402; A-side Matrix # PDS-402-A
        - Erotic Exotic - (I can) give you what you want, 1987; SR-14189; Erotic Exotic (Box 258)
          Catalog # SUD 0069C; A-side Matrix # SUD 069A C1 G1
          Sutra Records
        - Erotic Exotic - Take me as I am, 1986; SR-14190; Erotic Exotic (Box 258)
          Catalog # DMD 966; A-side Matrix # ST DM-50191-50188-2
        - Erste Allgemeine Verunsicherung - Küss die hard, schöne frau... (unzensierte maxi version), 1987; SR-14191; Erste Allgemeine Verunsicherung (Box 258)
          Catalog # 12C K 060-1 33425 6; A-side Matrix # 1334256-A1
          EMI Columbia Austria
          Austria
        - Erule - Listen up; Synopsis, 1994; SR-14192; Erule (Box 258)
          Catalog # PPRO-51100-1; A-side Matrix # PERTP1-A
          Pallas Records
        - Eruption - One way ticket, 1979; SR-14193; Eruption (Box 258)
          Catalog # PRO 7757; A-side Matrix # PRO-7757-AS LONG RE-1
          Ariola Records America
        - Escalators - Escalators, 1980; SR-14194; Escalators (Box 258)
          Catalog # UNE-500; A-side Matrix # UNE-500-A
          Unison Records
        - Escape Club - Wild, wild west, 1988; SR-14195; Escape Club (Box 258)
          Catalog # DMD 1210; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-5536455366-1
        - Escape From New York - Save our love; Slow beat, 1983; SR-14196; Escape From New York (Box 258)
          Catalog # PRO-7028; A-side Matrix # PRO-7028-A
          Profile Records
        - Escorts - All we need is another chance, 1973; SR-14197; Escorts (Box 258)
          Catalog # AR-9104; A-side Matrix # AR-9104-A+
          Alithia
          Bergen, New Jersey
        - Escovedo, Coke - Disco fantasy, 1977; SR-14198; Escovedo, Coke (Box 258)
          Catalog # SRM-1-1132; A-side Matrix # T 1 SRM-1-1132 A-2 CT
        - ESG - Moody; UFO, 2000; SR-14199; ESG (Box 258)
          Catalog # US LP 9-12; A-side Matrix # USLP 9-12 A1
          Universal Sound
        - ESG - Come away with ESG, 1983; SR-14200; ESG (Box 258)
          Catalog # 99-003LP; A-side Matrix # 99-003-LP-A
          99 Records
        - ESG - Moody; Starchild, SR-14201; ESG; Level 42 (Box 258)
          In same sleeve as # SR-12402. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # Rated "X" Records - 0:00; A-side Matrix # 0:00A
          Rated "X" Records
        - ESG - Moody; Starchild, SR-14202; ESG; Level 42 (Box 258)
          In same sleeve as # SR-12401. Multiple copies.
        - ESG - Sample credits don't pay our bills!, 1992; SR-14203; ESG (Box 258)
          Catalog # Nega 789; A-side Matrix # NEGA789A
          Nega Fulô Records
        - ESG - Swangin' and bangin', 1995; SR-14204; ESG (Box 258)
          Catalog # SPRO 50893; A-side Matrix # SPRO 50893 A
          Perrion Entertainment
        - E.S.P. - Wild thing; We got it, 1988; SR-14205; E.S.P. (Box 258)
          Catalog # FMS62324; A-side Matrix # FMS-62324-A
          Select Records
        - Essence Donn - Show me the way, 1994; SR-14206; Essence Donn (Box 258)
          Catalog # PVL 53174; A-side Matrix # MR-53174-A
          Freeze Records
        - Essence Donn - Show me the way, 1994; SR-14207; Essence Donn (Box 258)
        - Estefan, Gloria - Cherchez la femme, 1994; SR-14208; Estefan, Gloria (Box 258)
          Catalog # AED 7219; A-side Matrix # XSS 7219A-1A
          Epic
        - Estefan, Gloria - Como me duele perderte, 2000; SR-14209; Estefan, Gloria (Box 258)
          Catalog # EAS 16094; A-side Matrix # XSS-18094A
        - Estefan, Gloria - Out of nowhere, 2001; SR-14210; Estefan, Gloria (Box 258)
          Catalog # EAS 16494; A-side Matrix # XSS 16494 A
        - Estefan, Gloria - You'll be mine (party time), 1996; SR-14211; Estefan, Gloria (Box 258)
          Catalog # EAS 8158; A-side Matrix # XSS5158A-1B
        - Estefan, Gloria - Oye mi canto (hear my voice), 1990; SR-14212; Estefan, Gloria (Box 258)
          Catalog # 49 73169; A-side Matrix # XSS-73169A-1A
        - Gloria Estefan And Miami Sound Machine - 1-2-3, 1987; SR-14213; Gloria Estefan And Miami Sound Machine; Estefan, Gloria (Box 258)
          Catalog # EAS 1152; A-side Matrix # XSS 01152 A
        - Ester - Got to go, 1985; SR-14214; Ester (Box 258)
          Catalog # STU-412; A-side Matrix # #412
          Studio Records
          Oxon Hill, Maryland
        - Estes, Toni - Independant Lady, 2000; SR-14215; Estes, Toni; Lil' Zane (Box 258)
          Catalog # SPRO 81426; A-side Matrix # 08724-81426-17-B
        - Estes, Toni - Hot, 2000; SR-14216; Estes, Toni (Box 258)
          Catalog # SPRO 81334; A-side Matrix # 81334-1-A
        - Estus, Deon - Spell, 1988; SR-14217; Estus, Deon (Box 258)
          In same sleeve as # SR-12418. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # PRO 651-1; A-side Matrix # PRO-65-1-88NP-7751-LP-SP 1-1
          Mika Records
        - Estus, Deon - Spell, 1988; SR-14218; Estus, Deon (Box 258)
          In same sleeve as # SR-12417. Multiple copies.
        - Estus, Deon - Love hurts, 1984; SR-14219; Estus, Deon (Box 258)
          Catalog # LGYT 11; A-side Matrix # LGY(T)-11-A2
          Legacy Records
        - Etat Major - Django jet, 1982; SR-14220; Etat Major (Box 258)
          Catalog # 600560; A-side Matrix # 600560 A
          Mankin Records
        - Eternal - I wanna be the only one (Disc one), 1997; SR-14221; Eternal (Box 258)
          In same sleeve as # SR-12422. Double album.
          Catalog # 12EMDJD 472; A-side Matrix # 12 EMDJD472 A-01-01-1
        - Eternal - I wanna be the only one (Disc two), 1997; SR-14222; Eternal (Box 258)
          In same sleeve as # SR-12421. Double album.
        - Eternal - Sweet funky thing; Oh baby I..., 1994; SR-14223; Eternal (Box 258)
          Catalog # 8817886; A-side Matrix # 12 EM 353 A-1-1
          EMI United Kingdom
        - Ethos - Open up, 1977; SR-14224; Ethos (Box 258)
          Catalog # ST-11616; A-side Matrix # ST-1-11616-F6
          Capitol Records
        - E.T.'z - Ray came true; You don't stop, 1996; SR-14225; E.T.'z (Box 258)
          Catalog # ZLL97676; A-side Matrix # 97676-0007-1 A
          Zestland Records
        - E.T.'z - Ray came true; You don't stop, 1996; SR-14226; E.T.'z (Box 258)
        - EU (Musical group) - Livin' large, 1989; SR-14227; EU (Musical group) (Box 258)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14228. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 7 91021-1; A-side Matrix # STVR887261-C
        - EU (Musical group) - Livin' large, 1989; SR-14228; EU (Musical group) (Box 258)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14227. Multiple copies.
        - EU (Musical group) - Livin' large, 1989; SR-14229; EU (Musical group) (Box 258)
          Catalog # DMD 1413; A-side Matrix # STDM57788 57789-1
          Virgin Records America, Inc.
        - EU (Musical group) - Doing the cabbage patch, 1986; SR-14230; EU (Musical group) (Box 258)
          Catalog # TDE 3022; A-side Matrix # TDE-3022-A
          T.T.E.D. Records
          Washington D.C.
        - EU (Musical group) - Just the way you like it (Disc one), 1981; SR-14231; EU (Musical group) (Box 258)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14232. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # IC 7007; A-side Matrix # IC-7007-A
          Inner City Records Of Washington D.C.
        - EU (Musical group) - Just the way you like it (Disc one), 1981; SR-14232; EU (Musical group) (Box 258)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14231. Multiple copies.
        - EU (Musical group) - Future funk, 1986; SR-14233; EU (Musical group) (Box 258)
          Catalog # LP DANCE 1; A-side Matrix # LP DANCE 1 A1
          Be Bop & Fresh
        - EU (Musical group) - Sho nuff bump'n, 1985; SR-14234; EU (Musical group) (Box 258)
          Catalog # TDE-3010; A-side Matrix # TDE-3010-A
        - EU (Musical group) - Just the way you like it (Disc two), 1981; SR-14235; EU (Musical group) (Box 258)
          Catalog # IC 7008; A-side Matrix # IC-7008-A
        - EU (Musical group) - Livin' large, 1989; SR-14236; EU (Musical group) (Box 258)
        - EU (Musical group) - Doing the cabbage patch, 1986; SR-14237; EU (Musical group) (Box 258)
        - EU (Musical group) - E.U. freeze, 1985; SR-14238; EU (Musical group) (Box 258)
          Catalog # PRO-415; A-side Matrix # PRO 415-A
        - EU (Musical group) - 2 places at the same time, 1986; SR-14239; EU (Musical group) (Box 258)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14240. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 90536-1-Y; A-side Matrix # ST IL-866 075-B
          Island Records
        - EU (Musical group) - 2 places at the same time, 1986; SR-14240; EU (Musical group) (Box 258)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14239. Multiple copies.
        - EU (Musical group) - Da butt, 1988; SR-14241; EU (Musical group) (Box 259)
          Catalog # V-56083; A-side Matrix # V-1-56083-Z2
          EMI-Manhattan Records
        - EU (Musical group) - It's a family affair, 1986; SR-14242; EU (Musical group) (Box 259)
          Catalog # TDE 3021; A-side Matrix # TDE-3021-A
        - EU (Musical group) - Doing the cabbage patch, 1986; SR-14243; EU (Musical group) (Box 259)
        - EU (Musical group) - Rock yuh butt, 1988; SR-14244; EU (Musical group) (Box 259)
          Catalog # TDE-LP-3032; A-side Matrix # TDE-LP-3032-A-RE2
          Go Go USA Records
        - EU (Musical group) - Future funk, 1986; SR-14245; EU (Musical group) (Box 259)
        - EU (Musical group) - Go Ju Ju go, 1987; SR-14246; EU (Musical group) (Box 259)
          Catalog # BCR-0011; A-side Matrix # BCR-0011-A RE
          Big City Records
        - EU (Musical group) - Sho nuff bump'n, 1985; SR-14247; EU (Musical group) (Box 259)
        - EU (Musical group) - 2 places at the same time, 1986; SR-14248; EU (Musical group) (Box 259)
        - EU (Musical group) - Second time around; Come party with us, 1981; SR-14249; EU (Musical group) (Box 259)
          Catalog # VMC002; A-side Matrix # VMC-002-1
          Vermack Records
        - EU (Musical group) - It's a family affair, 1986; SR-14250; EU (Musical group) (Box 259)
        - Eugenix - Do it right, 1997; SR-14251; Eugenix (Box 259)
          Catalog # SMA 22; A-side Matrix # SMA+22+A
          Bear Necessities
        - Euro Funk - Everybody's dancing, 1981; SR-14252; Euro Funk (Box 259)
          Catalog # Ear-661; A-side Matrix # Ear-667-A
          Eargasm
          Miami, Florida
        - Euro Funk - Dynomite, 1981; SR-14253; Euro Funk (Box 259)
          Catalog # Ear-666; A-side Matrix # EAR-666-A
        - Euro-K - Swing it; Wild thang, 1988; SR-14254; Euro-K (Box 259)
          Catalog # AR 7648; A-side Matrix # AR 7648 A
          PIT Records
          Grand Rapids, Michigan
        - Eurythmics - Savage, 1987; SR-14255; Eurythmics (Box 259)
          Catalog # PL 71555; A-side Matrix # C-0035 A-1
          RCA
        - Eurythmics - Love is a stranger, 1982; SR-14256; Eurythmics (Box 259)
          Catalog # PC 5525; A-side Matrix # DAT 1 A-1U-1-1
        - Eurythmics - Be yourself tonight, 1985; SR-14257; Eurythmics (Box 259)
          Catalog # PL 70711; A-side Matrix # 39572 257A
        - Eurythmics - Sexcrime (nineteen eighty-four), 1984; SR-14258; Eurythmics (Box 259)
          Catalog # JW-13957; A-side Matrix # PW-13957A-1
        - Eurythmics - Sweet dream (are made of this), 1982; SR-14259; Eurythmics (Box 259)
          Catalog # JD-13502; A-side Matrix # Jd 13502A
        - Eurythmics - I need a man, 1987; SR-14260; Eurythmics (Box 259)
          Catalog # 6820-1-RDAB; A-side Matrix # 6820 1-RD-A-ES1
        - Eurythmics - Love is a stranger, 1982; SR-14261; Eurythmics (Box 259)
          Catalog # PW-13629; A-side Matrix # PW 13629A
        - Eurythmics - Right by your side, 1983; SR-14262; Eurythmics (Box 259)
          Catalog # JW-13696; A-side Matrix # PW-13696A-1
        - Eurythmics - There must be an angel (playing with my heart) (special dance mix!), 1985; SR-14263; Eurythmics (Box 259)
          Catalog # PT 40248 R; A-side Matrix # PT 40248 R A1
        - Evans, Adriana - Reality, 1996; SR-14264; Evans, Adriana (Box 259)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14265. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # RSP-64615-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-64615-1-A1
          PMP Records
        - Evans, Adriana - Reality, 1996; SR-14265; Evans, Adriana (Box 259)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14264. Multiple copies.
        - Evans, Adriana - Reality, 1996; SR-14266; Evans, Adriana (Box 259)
          Catalog # RDAB 64615-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-64615-1-A1
          BMG Entertainment
        - Evans, Faith - Again, 2005; SR-14267; Evans, Faith (Box 259)
          Catalog # SPRO 7087 6 19138 1 1; A-side Matrix # SPRO-19138-A
        - Evans, Faith - Soon as I get home, 1995; SR-14268; Evans, Faith (Box 259)
          Catalog # 78612-79041-1; A-side Matrix # 78612-79041-1-SA
          Bad Boy Entertainment
        - Evans, Richard - Do-re-me-for-soul (use it before you lose it), 1979; SR-14269; Evans, Richard (Box 259)
          Catalog # SP-12700; A-side Matrix # SP-12701-M1
          Horizon Records & Tapes
        - Evasions - Wikka wrap, 1981; SR-14270; Evasions (Box 259)
          Catalog # S-12339; A-side Matrix # S-12339A-1B
          Sam Records
        - Eve - Tambourine, 2007; SR-14271; Eve (Box 259)
          Catalog # GEFR 12113; A-side Matrix # GEFR 12113-1A
        - Eve - Don't stop it, 1994; SR-14272; Eve (Box 259)
          Catalog # 12-PO 234; A-side Matrix # 12-PO-234 A
          Ichiban Records
        - Ever-Ready - Flash light (P. funk medley), 1987; SR-14273; Ever-Ready (Box 259)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14274. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # LTW 8003; A-side Matrix # LTW-8003-A
          Liaison Records
          Beltsville, Maryland
        - Ever-Ready - Flash light (P. funk medley), 1987; SR-14274; Ever-Ready (Box 259)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14273. Multiple copies.
        - Everess - Don't you take your love, 1985; SR-14275; Everess (Box 259)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14276. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # AB9362; A-side Matrix # AB-9362-A
          Ace Beat Records
          Newark, New Jersey
        - Everess - Don't you take your love, 1985; SR-14276; Everess (Box 259)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14275. Multiple copies.
        - Everlast - Syndication; Bustin' loose, 1988; SR-14277; Everlast; Spinmasters (Box 259)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14278. Multiple copies.
          Catalog # 0-21027; A-side Matrix # 0-21027-A-SH2
        - Everlast - Syndication; Bustin' loose, 1988; SR-14278; Everlast; Spinmasters (Box 259)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14277. Multiple copies.
        - Everlast - Painkillers, 1998; SR-14279; Everlast (Box 259)
          Catalog # TB 342; A-side Matrix # TB 342-A
          Tommy Boy
        - Evers, Gaye - Body Party, 1979; SR-14280; Evers, Gaye; Nitelite (Box 259)
          Catalog # 8523 S96156; A-side Matrix # S33-96156 G-5
        - Everyday People - This kind of woman, 1990; SR-14281; Everyday People (Box 259)
          Catalog # 12SBK 14; A-side Matrix # 12 S3K 14 A-1J-1-1
          SBK Records
        - Everything But The Girl - Wrong, 1996; SR-14282; Everything But The Girl (Box 259)
          Catalog # 7243 8 93646 6 8; A-side Matrix # VST 1589 A-01-01-1
        - Everything But The Girl - Missing (the full remix EP), 1994; SR-14283; Everything But The Girl (Box 259)
          Catalog # NEG71T; A-side Matrix # NEG71TA3
          Blanco Y Negro
        - Ex Tras - Haven't been funked enough, 1983; SR-14284; Ex Tras (Box 259)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14285. Different discs.
          Catalog # TMTT 1; A-side Matrix # TMTT 1A
          TMT Records
        - Ex Tras - Haven't been funked enough, 1983; SR-14285; Ex Tras (Box 259)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14284. Different discs.
        - Exception - Slap you back, 1986; SR-14286; Exception (Box 259)
          Catalog # JS 1002; A-side Matrix # JS-1002-A
          Jump Street Records
        - Executioner - God bless you girls, 1994; SR-14287; Executioner (Box 259)
          Catalog # NK01735; A-side Matrix # NK-01735-A
          Nkoso Records
        - Executive - You got the stuff, 1981; SR-14288; Executive (Box 259)
          Catalog # TCD-123-DJ; A-side Matrix # TCD-123-AS-A-1S
          20th Century Fox Records
        - Exile - How could this go wrong, 1979; SR-14289; Exile (Box 259)
          Catalog # WBSD 8797; A-side Matrix # WBSD-8797-XXX-0879RE1-S-M1
        - Evil-Money - I like the way u move it, SR-14290; Evil-Money (Box 259)
          Catalog # AMG3001V; A-side Matrix # 7359-AMG3001V-1
          Asphalt Music Group
          Citrus Heights, California
        - Exotic Don - Cutt loose; Sexy thang, 1988; SR-14291; Exotic Don; Master Vic (Box 259)
          Catalog # PRO 464; A-side Matrix # PRO 464 A
        - Exotic Prince - Music that is in you, SR-14292; Exotic Prince (Box 259)
          Catalog # LP 715; A-side Matrix # 715-A
          RLA Record Company
        - Exotic Storm - I'm my own person, 1986; SR-14293; Exotic Storm (Box 259)
          Catalog # 49 06736; A-side Matrix # XSS-174041-1A
        - Explainer - Lorraine; Leave mih man, SR-14294; Explainer (Box 259)
          Catalog # SB-D 37; A-side Matrix # SB-D-37-A1
          Sun Burn
        - Exponential Enjoyment - Style introduction; Think for a moment!, 1990; SR-14295; Exponential Enjoyment (Box 259)
          Catalog # Tan 4004 0; A-side Matrix # TAN 4004-0-A
          TanTric Records
        - Extended Family - Ulysses, 1998; SR-14296; Extended Family (Box 259)
          Catalog # PAN 017; A-side Matrix # PAN 017 A-1-1
          PAN
        - Tha Eastsidaz - Got beef; Ghetto, 2000; SR-28950; Tha Eastsidaz (Box 273)
          Catalog # TVT-2044-0; A-side Matrix # TVT-2044-A
        - Egyptian Lover - Dance, 1985; SR-28951; Egyptian Lover (Box 273)
          Catalog # DMSR-00667; A-side Matrix # DMSR-00667-A
        - El Bravo, Johnny - Mundo moderno, 1972; SR-28952; El Bravo, Johnny (Box 273)
          Catalog # LPVS-1415; A-side Matrix # LPVS-1415-A
          Velvet
        - Electro Bounce - Electro Bounce, 1995; SR-28953; Electro Bounce (Box 273)
          Catalog # NU-1001; A-side Matrix # AR35220-A
          Nü Grüv Records
        - Elite Terrorists - OH-10: Aiming to blow; Wanna battle, 2000; SR-28954; Elite Terrorists (Box 273)
          Catalog # MC-0721; A-side Matrix # MC-721A
          Mission Control
          Cincinnati, Ohio
        - Ellis, Shirley - The clapping song, 1978; SR-28955; Ellis, Shirley (Box 273)
          Catalog # 12 MCEP 1; A-side Matrix # 12MCEP 1 A-1
        - Ellis, T.C. - Pussycat, 1991; SR-28956; Ellis, T.C. (Box 273)
          Catalog # PRO-A-4909; A-side Matrix # PRO A1-4909-SR1
          Paisley Park
        - Erotic Drum Band - Action '78 part 2-remix, 1978; SR-28957; Erotic Drum Band (Box 273)
          Catalog # CH-10002; A-side Matrix # CH-10005A-1S
          Montréal, Quebec
        - Estefan, Gloria - Live for loving you, 1991; SR-17627; Estefan, Gloria (Box 273)
          Catalog # AED 73971; A-side Matrix # XSS-73971-A-1A
        - Europeans - Recognition, 1983; SR-28958; Europeans (Box 273)
          Catalog # SP-17248; A-side Matrix # A&M SP017248 A ESI
          A&M Records
        - Eurythmics - Sisters are doin' it for themselves, 1985; SR-28959; Eurythmics; Franklin, Aretha (Box 273)
          Catalog # JW-14243; A-side Matrix # PW-14243-A-2
        - Evon Geffries & The Stand - Chapters: a novel by Evon Geffries & The Stand, 1988; SR-17628; Evon Geffries & The Stand (Box 273)
          Catalog # 81858-1; A-side Matrix # ST-A-886933-A 1-1
        - Exotic Taste - One time too many; Something in this world, 1982; SR-28960; Exotic Taste (Box 273)
          Catalog # GC 25; A-side Matrix # GC 22 A
          Garden City Records
          South Orange, New Jersey
        - Expert, Nadine - Excuse me monsieur, 1978; SR-28961; Expert, Nadine (Box 273)
          Catalog # 26 097 XOT; A-side Matrix # 26097-A 1135673-1-
          Fleet
        - Extince - 2e jeugd (Disc one), 2003; SR-14297; Extince (Box 273)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14298. Double album.
          Catalog # 7243 5 97206 1 6; A-side Matrix # 5972061 2A1
        - Extince - 2e jeugd (Disc two), 2003; SR-14298; Extince (Box 273)
          In same sleeve as # SR-14297. Double album.
          Catalog # 7243 5 97206 1 6; A-side Matrix # 5972061 1C1
        - Extra Curricular - Groove me, 1989; SR-14299; Extra Curricular (Box 273)
          Catalog # WAR 049; A-side Matrix # WAR-049-TONY-SP
          Idlers
        - Extra Strength - Who's the baddest, 1987; SR-14300; Extra Strength (Box 273)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # E007-A
          Longtime Running Records
          Brooklyn, New York